hhokit.co.uk 2015-06-08

# HHO Kit Privacy Policy

This privacy policy disclose you how we use personal information collected at this site. Our policy is to keep the personal information we receive from our site completely confidential and used solely for internal purposes. 

We will not share your personal information with any other parties. 

This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected by HHOKIT.ie

Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the HHOKIT.ie website. 

On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information (e.g Name, Address Email address e.t.c) collected at these pages will be held with the utmost care and will not be used in ways that you have not consented to. 

All collected information is retained for order processing and customer service only.

During your use of our website, we will collect non-identifying personal information to enhance the functionality of the website and to make your access more convenient and efficient. We retain non-identifying personal information and use it to establish website activity trends, monitor website performance, improve website design and functionality, fulfill orders, inform current and potential customers and suppliers about our services, and for other business purposes. 

Our collection of non-identifying personal information may involve the use of cookies. Among other uses, cookies allow us to deliver content specific to your interests, to save you from re-entering your registration data at each connection, and to provide features such as online customer payment and shopping carts. 

A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website HHOKIT.ie.

Use **VISA MASTER, AMERICAN, EXPRESS, DISCOVER, DIRECT DEBIT via Paypal.com** for purchasing operations. They are the authorized online retailer for our products.

Paypal.com will ask customers to supply various personal data when placing an order, such as name and address, credit-card information, and e-mail address. Paypal.com have their own Privacy Policy that explains how your information is processed and protected. All non-personally-identifying information and personally identifying-information described above is stored on restricted database servers.

HHOKIT.ie may change Privacy Policy from time to time. All changes will be affected on this page. If you have any questions about this policy or our site in general, please contact us.
